### Navigation

### Privacy Policy

Toxic Rain Studios LLC, the creator of Rise of Agon, is committed to protecting your privacy. Toxic Rain Studios LLC respects the privacy of its online visitors and users of Rise of Agon. Toxic Rain Studios LLC recognizes the importance of protecting any information collected from users and has adopted this privacy policy that guides how Toxic Rain Studios LLC gathers, stores, and uses information from the use of Toxic Rain Studios LLC online sites and Rise of Agon.

This Privacy Policy states our current privacy practices with regard to the information we collect when you interact with our online sites or install and play Rise of Agon. By accessing Toxic Rain Studios LLC online sites and/or installing and playing Rise of Agon, you acknowledge and fully understand Toxic Rain Studios LLC’ Privacy Policy and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is current as of its last revision date, February 8th, 2016. However, this policy may be amended from time to time to reflect changes and additions to the privacy policy. Please check back for the most current version before relying on any of the provisions in this privacy policy.  You continuing use of the Toxic Rain Studios LLC web site and products, including Rise of Agon, is your agreement to any changes to these policies.

#### Collection and Use of Information

By using Toxic Rain Studios LLC’ online sites or installing and playing Rise of Agon, users agree that Toxic Rain Studios LLC may collect aggregate information, individual information, and personally identifiable information, as defined below. Toxic Rain Studios LLC may share aggregate information and individual information with other parties. Toxic Rain Studios LLC shall not share personally identifiable information with other parties, except as described in the policy below.

**"Aggregate information"** is information that describes the habits, usage patterns, and demographics of users as a group but does not describe or reveal the identity of any particular user.

**"Individual information"** is information about a user that is presented in a form distinguishable from information relating to other users but not in a form that personally identifies any user or enables the recipient to communicate directly with any user unless agreed to by the user in advance of such communication. This information may be used to improve the installing and playing Rise of Agon and online sites, for internal marketing studies, or simply to collect demographic information about Toxic Rain Studios LLC’ users.

Toxic Rain Studios LLC may use customer contact information provided by users to send information about Toxic Rain Studios LLC, including news about product updates, contests, events, and other promotional materials, but only if the users agree to receive such communications. Except in the cases described below, Toxic Rain Studios LLC will not share personally identifiable information with any third party unless the user agrees to such disclosure in advance. "Personally identifiable information" consists of a user's name, email address, physical address, or other data about the user that enables the recipient to personally identify the user.

While Toxic Rain Studios LLC collects personally identifiable information on a voluntary basis, for certain products and online sites, Toxic Rain Studios LLC’ collection of personally identifiable information may be a requirement for access to Rise of Agon. Personally identifiable information will be processed and stored by Toxic Rain Studios LLC in databases.  Toxic Rain Studios LLC may allow third parties performing services under contract with Toxic Rain Studios LLC to access stored information but such access shall only be to the extent necessary to provide those services. In those instances, the third party will be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

In some situations, personally identifiable information you input in connection with Rise of Agon may be made available to other users of Rise of Agon. For example, during registration of Rise of Agon, Toxic Rain Studios LLC collects a user's email address and nickname, and at the user's option, first and last name.  Some of this information may be searchable and available to other users within Rise of Agon.

Toxic Rain Studios LLC has no obligation to keep the privacy of personally identifiable information that a user makes available to other users via Rise of Agon or other BToxic Rain Studios LLC software, such as in multiplayer or other public functions. If a user does not want to provide this information, the user may choose to opt out of providing this information. Additionally, if providing the information is a requirement of usage, the user may decline to use that particular service or product.

#### Associate and External Web Sites

Toxic Rain Studios LLC privacy policy does not extend to associates of Toxic Rain Studios LLC.  Furthermore, external web sites and companies with links to and from Toxic Rain Studios LLC’ online sites and products may collect personal information about users. Toxic Rain Studios LLC’ privacy policy does not extend to these external web sites and companies. Please refer directly to these companies and websites regarding their privacy policies. Toxic Rain Studios LLC may release personally identifiable information to comply with court orders or laws that require us to disclose such information.

#### Children Under The Age of 13

Toxic Rain Studios LLC will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from any person age 12 and under. Toxic Rain Studios LLC encourages parents to instruct their children to never give out personal information when online. Parents who are concerned about the transfer of personal information from their children may contact us at [support@bpgstudios.com](mailto:support@bpgstudios.com) to obtain a record of any information held by Toxic Rain Studios LLC and have it removed at their request.

#### Minors

Adolescents aged 13-17 years should ask their parents to read our Privacy Policy and to contact us if they would like any information on our guarantee of confidentiality or to comment on the content. Minors under 18 years of age should not order or subscribe to Rise of Agon or any paid service on-line without the permission of their parents or guardians. Parents and guardians should be particularly vigilant and to ensure that their minors do not transgress when using our sites or online services.

#### Cookies and Other Information on a User's Machine

Cookies are bits of electronic information that can be transferred to a user's hard drive to customize a person's usage of a product or online site, keep records of a user's access to an online site or product, or store information needed by the user on a regular basis.  Use of cookies is typically associated with web sites and online multiplayer games such as Rise of Agon. 

Toxic Rain Studios LLC may use cookies on our various web sites for tailoring user experiences as well as tracking users for the purposes of fraud and rule enforcement only. However this information is solely used for Toxic Rain Studios LLC and will not be sold or transmitted to another individual without consent of the user. Toxic Rain Studios LLC also does store information on a user's hard drive that is used in conjunction with online play of Rise of Agon. This includes a unique authorization key that is either entered by the user or downloaded automatically during product registration. This authorization key is used to identify a user as valid and allow access to Rise of Agon.  Information regarding billing, your account, your Internet connection and the Toxic Rain Studios LLC software installed on your computer are uploaded to the server in connection with your use of Rise of Agon software.

#### Bugs Reports

Toxic Rain Studios LLC software may automatically generate and submit to Toxic Rain Studios LLC bug reports upon a crash or other fault in the Toxic Rain Studios LLC software.  This automatically generated bug report information may include information about other software or hardware on a user's system.

Toxic Rain Studios LLC does not associate and store the automatically generated bug report information with personally identifiable information. Any bug reporting information manually submitted by users is associated and stored with personally identifiable information. Users should also be aware that game play information disclosed during multiplayer game play (e.g. player name and current player statistics) is public information and may be displayed to other users.

#### Chat Forums, Etc.

From time to time, Toxic Rain Studios LLC’ online products may provide chat forums, bulletin boards, or instant messaging tools to users. Any information that is disclosed in chat forums or bulletin boards is public information, and users who message one another may not know each other personally. Users should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in such chat forums.

#### Choice/Opt-out

Toxic Rain Studios LLC gives users the option of discontinuing receipt of promotional email communications from Toxic Rain Studios LLC as per Canadian Law. Instructions for discontinuing receipt of promotional email communications from Toxic Rain Studios LLCs will be provided in such subsequent email communications to users.

#### Storage and Security of Information

Personally identifiable information will be processed and stored by Toxic Rain Studios LLC in databases. Toxic Rain Studios LLC has taken reasonable steps to protect the information users share with us, including, but not limited to, setup of processes, equipment and software to avoid unauthorized access or disclosure of this information.

#### Contacting Big Picture Games

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or the privacy practices of Toxic Rain Studios LLC, please contact us at [support@bpgstudios.com](mailto:support@bpgstudios.com) or the following mailing address:

Big Picture Games Ltd.  
PO Box 23057 Bowmanville Mall  
Bowmanville, ON L1C5R4  
Canada
